NING-HSU WANG

Rm. B, 3F., No. 6, Ln. 1007, Daxue Rd., East Dist., Hsinchu City 300, Taiwan (R.O.C.) \diamond (+886)922105719 albert100121@gapp.nthu.edu.tw \diamond https://albert100121.github.io/ \diamond https://www.linkedin.com/in/ning-hsu-albert-wang/

RESEARCH INTERESTS

Topics: 3D Geometry, Robotics Perception, Computer Vision, Deep Learning

My current research focuses on 3D Geometry and Depth Estimation on 360°, Light-Field and shallow Depth of Field images with applications such as 3D Reconstruction and Robotic Perception.

EDUCATION

National Tsing Hua University

January 2018 - July 2020

- Master in Electrical Engineering
- Advised by Prof. Min Sun.
- GPA: 4.3/4.3

National Chiao Tung University

September 2013 - June 2017

- Bachelor in Mechanical Engineering
- GPA: 3.41/4.0, Ranking: 13/49, 25/99

PUBLICATIONS

360SD-Net: 360° Stereo Depth Estimation with Learnable Cost Volume, (ICRA 2020)

- Ning-Hsu Wang, Bolivar Solarte, Yi-Hsuan Tsai, Wei-Chen Chiu, Min Sun
- Short Version in ICCV 2019 360PI Workshop, Spotlight

We proposed a novel DNN targeting 360° stereo images. With this new task in Computer Vision, we presented two datasets for this task and achieved state-of-the-art among many representative baselines.

Indoor Panorama Planar 3D Reconstruction via Divide and Conquer, (CVPR 2021 Oral)

- Cheng Sun, Chi-Wei Hsiao, Ning-Hsu Wang, Min Sun, Hwann-Tzong Chen

We proposed a new benchmark for indoor panorama planar reconstruction by extending existing 360° datasets and and adopting state-of-the-art methods to the 360° datasets. We presented a new method which leverages the phenomenon of indoor human structures and 360° images and achieved state-of-the-art on the proposed benchmark.

Bridging Unsupervised and Supervised Depth from Focus via All-in-Focus Supervision

- In submission

AWARDS AND HONOR SOCIETY

The Phi Tau Phi Scholastic Honor Society of the Republic of China.

2020

- Honorary Member of the Society

Appier Conference Scholarship for Top Researches on Artificial Intelligence.

2020

EXPERIENCE

MediaTek

February 2020 - March 2021

- Computer Vision Research Intern

I worked as a research oriented internship with topics related to Stereo Matching, Disparity Estimation, Light-Field Camera, DoF (Depth of Field) Images and Blur/Bokeh Effects.

Vision Science Lab. National Tsing Hua University

January 2018 - July 2020

- Research Student, advised by Prof. Min Sun.

I mainly worked as the **project lead of 360° Stereo Depth Estimation**, co-advised by Prof. Wei-Chen Chiu and Dr. Yi-Hsuan Tsai. We proposed the Learnable Cost Volume to improve stereo depth estimation on 360° images (**ICRA 2020**). I also worked on **Planar Reconstruction**, co-advised by Prof. Hwann-Tzong Chen. We proposed a new method as well as a new benchmark on indoor panorama planar reconstruction (**CVPR 2021 oral**).

- Contestant

I worked as the technical lead in this nationwide startup competition, which includes the following stages: Garage Party, Elevator Pitch, Workshop. We won the **Second Place Award** in the Garage Party stage.

Atos August 2017

- On-site Engineer
- 29th Summer Universiade internet system maintenance.

PROJECT HIGHLIGHTS

3D Horror Scene: Horror Style Transfer Using 360° Views and 3D Reconstruction

- Collection of horror scene data.
- Implementation of CycleGAN for style transfer.
- Implementation of **LayoutNet** for 360° layout reconstruction.

Design and implementation of Logistic UAV (Unmanned Aerial Vehicle)

- Design and implementation of UAV mechanism.
- Design and implementation of unloading mechanism and motor control system.
- Design of UAV surveillance system.
- Demostration of UAV control for unseen location object unloading.

Object Searching Robot Design

- Design and implementation of KNR mechanism and ultrasonic avoidance system.
- LabVIEW programming of motor control, sensor feedback and image processing.

Validation of The Lambda Method for Integer Ambiguity Estimation

- Implementation of The Lambda Method for Integer Ambiguity Estimation with Matlab simulation.

ABILITIES AND CERTIFICATIONS

Programming Python, C/C++, HTML, CSS

DL Framework Pytorch, TensorFlow

Software & Tools LabVIEW: Industrial Control & Simulation

Matlab: Mathematics Simulation LTSpice: Electrical Circuit Simulation

ANSYS-Fluent: Computational Fluid Dynamics Simulation

AutoCAD, Solidworks: Computer-aided Design Drafting Software

Hardware Arduino, 8051

Misc. OpenCV, Github, Vim, Linux, LATEX

Language Fluent in Mandarin (Native)

Proficient in English, TOEIC Golden Certification (Score: 900)

Elementary Proficiency in Japanese (4 semesters)